[
    {
        "question": "What did the Avengers eat after the invasion of New York?",
        "choice1": "Schawarma",
        "choice2": "Pizza",
        "choice3": "Samosas",
        "choice4": "Falafel",
        "answer": 1
    },
    
    {
        "question": "How many in-person cameos has Stan Lee done for the MCU?",
        "choice1": "20",
        "choice2": "21",
        "choice3": "22",
        "choice4": "24",
        "answer": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "Who takes over the Black Widow mantle after Natasha Romanoff?",
        "choice1": "Alexei Shostakov",
        "choice2": "Melina Vostokoff",
        "choice3": "Yelena Belova",
        "choice4": "Kate Bishop",
        "answer": 3
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Who founded the Time Variance Authority?",
        "choice1": "The Collector",
        "choice2": "Emil Blonsky",
        "choice3": "Aldrich Killian",
        "choice4": "Nathaniel Richards",
        "answer": 4
    },
    
    {
        "question": "What year does Avengers: Endgame take place in?",
        "choice1": "2022",
        "choice2": "2023",
        "choice3": "2024",
        "choice4": "2025",
        "answer": 2
    },
    
    {
        "question": "What universe does the MCU take place in?",
        "choice1": "813",
        "choice2": "98",
        "choice3": "Earth-2",
        "choice4": "616",
        "answer": 4
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Who caused Nick Fury to loose his eye?",
        "choice1": "Hank Pym",
        "choice2": "Ronan the Accuser",
        "choice3": "Alexander Pierce",
        "choice4": "Goose",
        "answer": 4
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Who is Thor's mother?",
        "choice1": "Sylvie",
        "choice2": "Hela",
        "choice3": "Frigga",
        "choice4": "Sersi",
        "answer": 3
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Star-Lord is half-human and half what?",
        "choice1": "Kree",
        "choice2": "Elfian",
        "choice3": "Celestial",
        "choice4": "Inhuman",
        "answer": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "Who introduced Wanda Maximoff to dark magic",
        "choice1": "Evanora",
        "choice2": "Agatha",
        "choice3": "Clea",
        "choice4": "Dr. Strange",
        "answer": 2
    }
]